<START:person> GODWIN NGUSEN JETHRO <END>
FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER | <START:location> ABUJA, NIGERIA <END> | +2348067906140
<START:link> godwinjethro@gmail.com <END> | <START:link> https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro <END> | <START:link> Github <END>
<SPLIT>
<START:heading> PERSONAL DATA <END>
Date of Birth: <START:date> 28th December, 1995 <END>
Gender: Male
First Name: <START:person> Godwin <END>
Middle Name: <START:person> Ngusen <END>
Last Name: <START:person> Jethro <END>
Marital Status: Single
Nationality: <START:location> Nigeria <END>
State of Origin: <START:location> Plateau <END>
Local Government Area: Bokkos
Place of Birth: <START:location> Jos <END>
Interests: Sport, Reading and Travelling
<SPLIT>
<START:heading> KEY SKILLS <END>
Highly skilled and innovative Software Engineer with <START:date> 5+ years <END> of experience. Adept at translating system designs into robust, optimized code using <START:skills> Java Spring Boot <END> and <START:skills> Angular frameworks <END> to deliver efficient APIs and user-friendly interfaces. Proven track record of driving success across diverse industries, including <START:skills> Human Capital Management <END> and <START:skills> e-Agro <END>. Passionate about creating scalable, maintainable code and staying current with industry best practices and emerging technologies. Dedicated to delivering high-performance, visually appealing web solutions that elevate brands and exceed user expectations.
<SPLIT>
<START:heading> KEY SKILLS <END>
• Programming Markup Languages: <START:skills> Java <END>, <START:skills> JavaScript <END>, <START:skills> TypeScript <END>, <START:skills> HTML <END>, <START:skills> CSS <END>
• Databases: <START:skills> MySQL <END>, <START:skills> PostgreSQL <END>, <START:skills> MongoDB <END>, <START:skills> JDBC <END>, <START:skills> JPA <END>, <START:skills> R2DBC <END>
• DevOps: <START:skills> GitHub actions <END>, <START:skills> Docker <END>, <START:skills> Docker hub <END>, <START:skills> Jenkins <END>, <START:skills> Firebase Cloud Messaging <END>, <START:skills> Consul <END>, <START:skills> AWS <END>
• Frameworks: <START:skills> Spring Boot <END> (<START:skills> Reactive WebFlux <END>, <START:skills> Mockito <END>, <START:skills> JUnit <END>), <START:skills> Angular <END> (<START:skills> Material <END>, <START:skills> NgRx <END>, <START:skills> RxJS <END>)
• Collaboration and Project Management Tools: <START:skills> Jira <END>, <START:skills> Slack <END>, <START:skills> Microsoft Teams <END>, <START:skills> Google Meet <END>
• Soft Skills:
  - Effective communication skill between colleagues, resulting in a 40% reduction in project delays and a 20% increase in overall team productivity
  - Excellent Time Management Skill to execute given tasks and achieve desired goals
  - Problem-solving and critical thinking
  - Outstanding Emotional Intelligence and a positive team player
<SPLIT>
<START:heading> PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE <END>
<START:position> Backend Software Engineer <END>
<START:organization> PYRANEX HQ LIMITED <END>, <START:location> ABUJA, NIGERIA <END> (REMOTE)
<START:date> Jan 2024 – Present <END>










<START:organization> Sohclick Technology Limited <END> (Remote) <START:date> Jan 2022 – Present <END>
• Developed and optimized backend pipelines for <START:skills> LLM integration <END>, focusing on performance and reliability.
• Validated and tested LLM outputs, enhancing response accuracy by over 25%.
• Worked with open-source datasets, delivering real-time, targeted AI results.
• Collaborated on AI model fine-tuning and custom NLP applications.
• Tools & Technologies Used: <START:skills> Python, SQL, AWS, Hugging Face, OpenAI API, React, Next.js <END>.
<START:role> Software Developer <END>
<START:organization> Sohclick Technology Limited <END>, <START:location> Jos, Plateau State <END> <START:date> Jan 2021 – Dec 2022 <END>
• Built client applications as a junior developer and collaborated on complex projects.
• Designed responsive web applications using <START:skills> JavaScript and TypeScript <END>.
• Reviewed and tested applications for cross-browser compatibility and device adaptability.
• Technologies Used: <START:skills> ReactJs, NextJs, Angular Material, NGRX, Angular, Tailwind CSS, Git <END>.
<START:role> Software Developer <END>
<START:organization> Heroyfoods Ltd. <END>, <START:location> Jos, Nigeria (Remote) <END> <START:date> Jan 2020 – Sept 2020 <END>
• Developed high-quality, scalable fintech solutions, enhancing usability by 30%.
• Optimized web pages, improving performance by 25%.
• Collaborated across teams to ensure timely product delivery.
• Technologies Used: <START:skills> ReactJs, NextJs, Tailwind CSS, Git <END>.
<START:role> Fullstack Developer (Personal Projects & Freelance) <END>
<START:location> Remote <END> <START:date> Jun 2018 – Dec 2019 <END>
• Built a personal portfolio showcasing frontend and backend projects.
• Collaborated on a part-time contract to develop a <START:skills> CarFlix application <END>, showcasing cars for sale.
• Designed login/signup pages and integrated user authentication.
• Technologies Used: <START:skills> HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NextJs, NodeJs <END>.
<START:heading> Education <END>
<START:organization> University of Jos <END>, <START:location> Jos, Plateau State, Nigeria <END>
<START:degree> B.Sc.(Ed) – Computer Science <END> <START:date> Graduated: 2022 <END>
