GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
Typescript I-SKILL
, O
Angular I-SKILL
, O
Angular Material I-SKILL
, O
NgRx I-SKILL
, O
RxJs I-SKILL
, O
ReactJs I-SKILL
, O
TailwindCSS I-SKILL
, O
Material Designs I-SKILL
, O
PrimeNG I-SKILL
. O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL I-SKILL
, O
and O
MongoDB I-SKILL
. O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Github actions I-SKILL
, O
Jira I-SKILL
, O
Trello I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft Azure I-SKILL
, O
AWS I-SKILL
, O
Slack I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft teams I-SKILL
. O
PROFESSIONAL B-SECTION
WORK I-SECTION
EXPERIENCE I-SECTION
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
PYRANEX B-ORG
HQ I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE) O
Oct B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
– O
Present I-DATE
GODWIN B-PER
NGUSEN I-PER
JETHRO I-PER
FULL-STACK O
SOFTWARE O
ENGINEER O
| O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2348067906140 O
godwinjethro@gmail.com O
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-jethro O
| O
Github O
PERSONAL O
DATA O
Date O
of O
Birth O
: O
28th O
December O
, O
1995 O
Gender O
: O
Male O
First O
Name O
: O
Godwin B-PER
Middle O
Name O
: O
Ngusen B-PER
Last O
Name O
: O
Jethro B-PER
Marital O
Status O
: O
Single O
Nationality O
: O
Nigeria B-LOC
State O
of O
Origin O
: O
Plateau B-LOC
Local O
Government O
Area O
: O
Bokkos B-LOC
Place O
of O
Birth O
: O
Jos B-LOC
Interests O
: O
Sport O
, O
Reading O
and O
Travelling O
CAREER O
SUMMARY O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
5+ O
years O
of O
experience O
. O
Adept O
at O
translating O
system O
designs O
into O
robust O
, O
optimized O
code O
using O
Java O
Spring O
Boot O
and O
Angular O
frameworks O
to O
deliver O
efficient O
APIs O
and O
user-friendly O
interfaces O
. O
Iniubong B-PER
Uko I-PER
Udofot I-PER
+2348024983733 O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
iniubongudofot2000@gmail.com O
Professional O
Summary O
: O
• O
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Fullstack O
Software O
Engineer O
with O
4 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
developing O
robust O
web O
applications O
and O
2 O
years O
of O
hands- O
on O
expertise O
with O
Large O
Language O
Models O
(LLMs) O
and O
AI O
systems O
. O
Proficient O
in O
JavaScript O
, O
TypeScript O
, O
and O
Python O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
command O
of O
frontend O
technologies O
like O
React O
and O
Next.js O
, O
and O
backend O
capabilities O
in O
Node.js O
. O
At O
SohClick B-LOC
Technology O
, O
led O
the O
integration O
of O
advanced O
AI O
and O
LLM-driven O
solutions O
, O
enhancing O
user O
experiences O
and O
optimizing O
operational O
workflows O
. O
Proven O
track O
record O
in O
driving O
success O
across O
diverse O
industries O
, O
including O
banking O
and O
fintech O
, O
through O
scalable O
, O
maintainable O
code O
and O
high-performance O
solutions O
that O
exceed O
expectations O
. O
Committed O
to O
staying O
at O
the O
forefront O
of O
emerging O
technologies O
and O
adept O
at O
tackling O
complex O
challenges O
with O
a O
performance-driven O
approach O
. O
Skills O
• O
HTML O
, O
CSS O
, O
JavaScript/Typescript O
, O
RxJs O
, O
ReactJs O
, O
Angular O
, O
Angular O
Material O
, O
NgRx O
, O
TailwindCSS O
, O
Material O
Designs O
, O
PrimeNG O
. O
• O
NodeJs O
, O
Express O
, O
Python O
, O
Java O
. O
• O
MySQL O
, O
PostgreSQL O
, O
and O
MongoDB O
• O
Git O
, O
Github O
actions O
, O
Jira O
, O
Trello O
, O
Microsoft O
Azure O
, O
AWS O
, O
Slack O
, O
Microsoft O
teams O
. O
• O
Effective O
communication O
skill O
between O
colleagues O
, O
resulting O
in O
a O
40% O
reduction O
in O
project O
delays O
and O
a O
20% O
increase O
in O
overall O
team O
productivity O
• O
Excellent O
Time O
Management O
Skill O
to O
execute O
give O
task O
and O
achieve O
desired O
goals O
• O
Problem O
solving O
and O
critical O
thinking O
• O
Outstanding O
Emotional O
Intelligence O
, O
and O
positive O
team O
player O
Professional O
Experience O
HNG O
Internship O
, O
ABUJA B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
(REMOTE O
) O
Aug O
2024 O
– O
Oct O
2024 O
Intern O
Frontend O
Software O
Engineer O
• O
Developed O
high-quality O
, O
responsive O
and O
scalable O
solutions O
JETHRO B-PER
Godwin I-PER
No B-LOC
20 I-LOC
F.D.A I-LOC
Road I-LOC
Dadin I-LOC
Kowa I-LOC
Jos I-LOC
Plateau I-LOC
State I-LOC
| O
Email O
: O
godwinjethro@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
Tel O
: O
08067906140 B-PHONE
| O
Github O
: O
https://github.com/Godwin-munan B-URL
CAREER O
OBJECTIVE O
To O
find O
a O
position O
to O
meet O
my O
competences O
, O
skills O
, O
education O
and O
experience O
, O
and O
to O
contribute O
add O
value O
to O
the O
productive O
workforce O
of O
any O
organization O
employed O
to O
work O
in O
and O
to O
achieve O
career O
growth O
. O
WORK O
EXPERIENCE O
GALAXY B-ORG
BACKBONE I-ORG
15th B-DATE
July I-DATE
- I-DATE
22nd I-DATE
Sept I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Position O
: O
Internship B-POSITION
MODERN B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
SERVICE I-ORG
AND I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
– I-DATE
November I-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Position O
: O
ICT B-POSITION
Support I-POSITION
Staff I-POSITION
SOHCLICK B-ORG
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
– I-DATE
Present I-DATE
Position O
: O
Junior B-POSITION
Developer I-POSITION
VICTOR B-PER
DAODU I-PER
OLAOLUWA I-PER
FRONTEND B-POSITION
SOFTWARE I-POSITION
ENGINEER I-POSITION
| O
LAGOS B-LOC
, O
NIGERIA B-LOC
| O
+2349021489349 B-PHONE
daoduvictor48@gmail.com B-EMAIL
| O
https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-daodu B-URL
| O
Github O
CAREER B-OBJ
SUMMARY I-OBJ
Highly O
skilled O
and O
innovative O
Frontend B-POSITION
Software I-POSITION
Engineer I-POSITION
with O
4 B-DURATION
years I-DURATION
of O
experience O
. O
SKILLS B-SECTION
HTML B-SKILL
, O
CSS I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript I-SKILL
/ I-SKILL
